A Guide to the Adèle Goodman Clark papers, 1849-1978
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series V: Virginia League of Women Voters, undated, 1915-1967
  - Subseries A: President/Executive Secretary Correspondence, undated, 1920-1944
    - January - March, 1927 (Box 72)
    - April - June, 1927 (Box 73)
    - July - September, 1927 (Box 73)
    - October - December, 1927 (Box 73)
    - January - March, 1928 (Box 73)
    - April - May, 1928 (Box 73)
    - June, 1928 (Box 73)
    - July - August, 1928 (Box 73)
    - September - December, 1928 (Box 73)
    - January - March, 1929 (Box 74)
    - April - June, 1929 (Box 74)
    - July - September, 1929 (Box 74)
    - October - December, 1929 (Box 74)
    - January, 1930 (Box 74)
    - February - March, 1930 (Box 74)
    - April - June, 1930 (Box 74)
    - July - September, 1930 (Box 74)
    - October - December, 1930 (Box 75)
    - January - March, 1931 (Box 75)
    - April - June, 1931 (Box 75)
    - July - September, 1931 (Box 75)
    - October - December, 1931 (Box 75)
    - January - February, 1932 (Box 75)
    - March - April, 1932 (Box 75)
    - May - June, 1932 (Box 75)
    - July - September, 1932 (Box 76)
    - October - December, 1932 (Box 76)
    - January - March, 1933 (Box 76)
    - April - June, 1933 (Box 76)
    - July - September, 1933 (Box 76)
    - October - December, 1933 (Box 76)
    - January - May, 1934 (Box 76)
    - June - December, 1934 (Box 76)
    - January - March, 1935 (Box 76)
    - April - December, 1935 (Box 76)
    - 1936-1944 (Box 77)
    - undated material (Box 77)
  - Subseries B: Board of Directors/Executive Committee/General Council/Standing/Special Committees File, undated, 1921-1934
    - Board of Directors (Box 77)
      - Agendas (Box 77)
      - Correspondence (Box 77)
        - 1921-1923 (Box 77)
        - 1924-1925 (Box 77)
        - 1926 (Box 77)
      - Correspondence (Box 78)
        - 1927 (Box 78)
        - 1928-1929 (Box 78)
        - 1930-1935 (Box 78)
        - 1921-1923 (Box 78)
        - 1921-1923 (Box 78)
      - Memoranda, 1920-1938 (Box 78)
      - Minutes (Box 78)
        - 1920-1923 (Box 78)
        - 1924-1925 (Box 78)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 78)
        - 1928 (Box 78)
      - Pre-Convention Board Meeting Minutes, undated, 1925 (Box 79)
      - Post Convention Board Meeting Minutes, 1924-1925 (Box 79)
      - Programs, undated (Box 79)
      - Resolutions, undated, 1921, 1925 (Box 79)
    - Executive Council (Box 79)
      - Minutes, 1923, 1925 (Box 79)
      - Minutes--Pre-Convention, undated (Box 79)
    - Executive Committee (Box 79)
      - Agendas, 1923-1932 (Box 79)
      - Correspondence, 1921-1933 (Box 79)
      - Memoranda, undated, 1921-1933 (Box 79)
      - Minutes, 1921-1928 (Box 79)
      - Minutes, 1929-1933 (Box 79)
      - Resolutions, 1932 (Box 79)
    - General Council (Box 79)
      - Memoranda, undated, 1932 (Box 79)
      - Pre-Convention Meetings, 1926-1930 (Box 79)
    - Standing/Special Committees (Box 79)
      - Capitol Committee--Minutes, 1924 (Box 79)
      - Child Welfare Committee (Box 79)
        - Bulletins, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1921-1925, 1926-1934 (Box 79)
        - Infant Welfare and Maternity Questionnaires, 1925 (Box 79)
        - Reports, undated (Box 79)
      - Constitution Revision Committee--Correspondence and Report, 1922 (Box 80)
      - Education, Committee on (Box 80)
        - American Citizenship Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 80)
          - Bulletins, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, undated, 1920-1933 (Box 80)
          - Report, undated, 1925, 1928 (Box 80)
      - Efficiency in Government, Department of (See also: Series VII, Subseries B) (Box 80)
        - Election Laws and Methods, 1920 (Box 80)
          - General Correspondence, 1921-1931 (Box 80)
          - Memoranda and Reports, undated, 1920-1932 (Box 80)
        - Efficiency in Government Conference (Box 80)
          - Addresses, 1921 (Box 80)
          - Announcements, Lists, Notes, Program Agendas, Resolutions, Miscellaneous 1921 (Box 80)
      - Efficiency in Government, Committee on (Box 81)
        - Efficiency in Government Conference (Box 81)
          - Correspondence September - October, 1921 (Box 81)
          - Correspondence November, 1921 - June 1922 (Box 81)
          - Correspondence--"Survey of the Voters Mind," 1922-1926 (Box 81)
      - "Get Out the Vote" Campaign--Bulletins, Correspondence, Instructions Reports, 1922-1926 (Box 81)
      - Interracial Cooperation Material--Correspondence, Pamphlets, Reports, Miscellaneous, 1921-1928 (Box 81)
      - International Cooperation to Prevent War, Committee on (Box 81)
        - Bulletins and Correspondence, 1921-1922, 1923 (Box 81)
      - International Cooperation to Prevent War, Committee on (Box 82)
        - Bulletins and Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 82)
        - Bulletins, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, undated, 1926-1932 (Box 82)
        - Louisa K. Fast Virginia Tour [Includes Correspondence, Itineraries, Memoranda (Box 82)
        - Newspaper Clippings] October, 1930 (Box 82)
        - Newspaper Clippings [fragile materials], undated (Box 82)
        - Reports, undated (Box 82)
      - International Cooperation to Prevent War, Conference on the Cause and Cure of War (Box 82)
        - Delegate Lists, Memoranda, Notes, Reports, undated, 1928 (Box 82)
        - Reports, undated (Box 82)
      - Joint Executive Committee (Virginia and Richmond)--Minutes, 1921 (Box 82)
      - Legal Status of Women, Committee on--Bulletins, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1921-1931 (Box 82)
      - Living Costs, Committee on [Food Supply and Demand]--General Correspondence, Reports, Miscellaneous, 1921-1931 (Box 82)
      - Membership Extension Committee--Minutes and Program, 1932 (Box 82)
      - New Voters, Committee on (Box 82)
        - Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports (Box 82)
          - 1925 (Box 82)
          - 1926-1928 [Miss Jeffires Heinrich, Chair] (Box 82)
      - Organization Committee (Box 83)
        - Correspondence, Minutes, Notes, undated, 1920 (Box 83)
        - Correspondence and Questionnaires, 1920-1923 (Box 83)
        - Correspondence, 1925-1926 [Chair Pro Tem Mrs. John T. Lewis] (Box 83)
      - Press Department [Press Chair/Publicity Director]--Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 83)
        - Publications, 1921-1931
      - Primary Committee on Elections, 1922 (Box 83)
      - Prison Conditions/Farm Committee--Bulletins, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings (Box 83)
      - 1922-1927 (Box 83)
      - Public Health, Committee on, 1925 (Box 83)
      - Resolutions Committee--Reports, 1921-1922 (Box 83)
      - Social Hygiene, Committee on--Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports, Miscellaneous (Box 83)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 83)
      - State-Wide Membership Committee--Minutes, 1932 (Box 83)
      - Steering Committee [Prospective League of Women Voters]--Correspondence, Minutes, 1946 (Box 83)
      - Uniform Laws, Committee on--Bulletins, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1921-1923 (Box 83)
      - Women in Industry, Committee on (Box 83)
        - Correspondence, Reports, Miscellaneous, 1920-1933 (Box 83)
        - Correspondence--"Shorter Day and Women Workers," 1923-1930 (Box 83)
  - Subseries C: State/National League Convention Material, undated, 1921-1933
    - State League Conventions (Box 84)
      - Ballots, undated, 1923, 1929 (Box 84)
      - Biennial Convention, 1933 (Box 84)
      - Committee Reports and Recommendations (Box 84)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 84)
        - 1924-1926 (Box 84)
        - 1927-1931 (Box 84)
      - Convention (Box 84)
        - Chair Correspondence [Mrs. S.S. Matthews], 1924 (Box 84)
        - Rules Committee, 1928 (Box 84)
        - Site Brochures, undated, 1930-1933 (Box 84)
      - Delegate/Visitor Correspondence and Lists [Prospective], 1922-1923 (Box 84)
      - Delegate/Visitor Correspondence and Lists [Prospective], 1924-1933 (Box 84)
      - Executive/Headquarters Secretary Reports, 1922-1929 (Box 84)
      - Finance Committee--Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 84)
      - Minutes and Reports, undated, 1923-1929 (Box 84)
      - Notes, undated (Box 85)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated, 1923-1924 (Box 85)
      - Nominating Committee [includes correspondence], 1925-1933 (Box 85)
      - Pledges [National and State], 1922-1930 (Box 85)
      - Program Committee--Correspondence (Box 85)
        - 1924 (Box 85)
        - 1925 (Box 85)
        - 1926 [Lynchburg] (Box 85)
        - 1927 (Box 85)
        - 1928 (Box 85)
        - 1929 (Box 85)
      - Programs, undated, 1922-1931 (Box 85)
      - Resolutions, undated, 1923 (Box 85)
      - Speeches, undated, 1924-1929 (Box 85)
      - Tenth Anniversary Convention--Newspaper clippings, 1930 (Box 86)
      - Tenth Anniversary Convention--Registration Book, 1930 (Box 86)
      - Tenth Annual--Convention Drama "Decade of League Work" by Adèle Clark, 1930 (Box 86)
    - National League Conventions (Box 86)
      - Cleveland--Correspondence, Memoranda, Newspaper Articles, Reports, Resolutions,Miscellaneous, 1921 (Box 86)
      - Baltimore [Pan American Conference]--Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1922 (Box 86)
      - Des Moines--Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1923 (Box 86)
      - Buffalo--Correspondence, Delegate Lists, Miscellaneous, 1924 (Box 86)
      - Richmond (Box 86)
        - Announcements, Programs, Resolutions, Miscellaneous, undated, 1924-1925 (Box 86)
        - Commonwealth Club Dinner, undated (Box 86)
        - Delegate Correspondence and Lists March--April, 1925 (Box 86)
        - Delegate and Visitor Lists, undated (Box 86)
        - Gala Finance Luncheon, 1925 (Box 86)
        - General Chairman Report, undated (Box 86)
        - Local Committee Expense Statement and Financial Report, 1925 (Box 86)
        - Memoranda, Notes and Reports, undated, 1924 (Box 86)
        - Newspaper Clippings, 1925 (Box 86)
        - Notes [by Adèle Clark], undated (Box 86)
        - Official Visitors Correspondence March - April, 1925 (Box 87)
        - Pledge Distribution List, 1925 (Box 87)
        - Program Committee Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 87)
        - "Special Visitor" Plan, undated (Box 87)
        - Staff Conference, Minutes, Notes, 1925 (Box 87)
        - Woman Citizen article, 1925 (Box 87)
      - St.Louis--Correspondence, Memoranda, Newspaper clippings and Miscellaneous, undated, 1926 (Box 87)
  - Subseries D: Financial Material, undated, 1921-1939
    - Book of Possibilities, undated (Box 87)
    - Budget [Committee?] Report November, 1920 (Box 87)
    - Finance, Committee on (Box 87)
      - Finance Chair--Correspondence and Memoranda, 1921-1925, 1926, 1927-1928 (Box 87)
      - Finance, Committee on (Box 88)
        - Finance Chair--Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1935 (Box 88)
        - Individual and Local League Pledge and Quota Lists, undated, 1923-1935 (Box 88)
        - Recommendations and Reports of Finance Chair, undated, 1929 (Box 88)
      - Treasurer, Office of (Box 88)
        - Correspondence, 1921-1939 (Box 88)
        - Notes, undated, 1921 (Box 88)
        - Reports, undated, 1921-1928 (Box 88)
      - Cashbook, 1922-1923 (Box 89)
      - Comparison Liabilities, 1924-1925 (Box 89)
      - Expenditures and Receipts, 1934-1936 (Box 89)
      - Financial History, undated (Box 89)
      - Financial Statements, 1922-1932 (Box 89)
      - Lease Agreements, 1922-1927 (Box 89)
      - Ledger Sheets--Receipts and Disbursements, 1920-1921 (Box 89)
      - Statement of Operations, 1921-1923 (Box 89)
  - Subseries E: Legislative Material, undated, 1921-1944
    - Bill Abstracts and Summaries, undated (Box 89)
    - Children's Code Commission (Box 90)
      - Correspondence, Drafts of Bills, Consent Laws, Questionnaires, Miscellaneous, 1921, 1921-1923 (Box 90)
    - Legislative Committee (Box 90)
      - Bulletins, Circulars, Correspondence Legislative Chair, 1920-1921, 1922 (Box 90)
    - Legislative Committee (Box 90)
      - Bulletins, Circulars, Correspondence Legislative Chair, 1923, 1925, 1926-1936 (Box 90)
    - Legislative Committee (Box 91)
      - Reports and Summaries, undated, 1920-1929 (Box 91)
    - Legislation Measures and Programs (Box 91)
      - Candidate's/Legislator's Replies, 1921-1922, 1923 (Box 91)
    - Legislation Measures and Programs (Box 91)
      - Candidates's Replies, 1925-1927, 1929-1932 (Box 91)
    - Legislation Measures and Programs (Box 92)
      - Candidate's Replies, 1932 (Box 92)
    - Legislation Measures and Programs (Box 92)
      - Candidates's Replies, 1933-1934, 1935-1937 (Box 92)
      - Correspondence, Candidates/Legislators Responses to Questionnaires, 1922-1938 (Box 92)
    - Virginia Women's Council of Legislative Chairmen of State Organizations (Box 92)
      - Legislative Chair: M.E. Pidgeon, May I. Moore--Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 92)
      - Bulletins, Calendars of Legislation, Circulars, Lists, Reports, Miscellaneous, 1923-1944 (Box 92)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1920-1934 (Box 93)
  - Subseries F: Local District/League Material, undated, 1920-1934
    - City Leagues (Box 93)
      - Alexandria Branch--Correspondence, 1920-1928 (Box 93)
      - Bristol VA/TN--Correspondence, report, 1921-1929 (Box 93)
      - Craddock League, 1923-1932 (Box 93)
      - Crozet League, 1924-1925 (Box 93)
      - Farmville League, 1920-1927 (Box 93)
      - Fredricksburg--Correspondence, 1920-1924 (Box 93)
      - Front Royal, 1926 (Box 93)
      - Hampton, 1921-1922 (Box 93)
      - Harrisonburg, 1920-1924 (Box 93)
      - Hopewell--City Point, 1923 (Box 93)
      - Lynchburg--Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 93)
      - Lynchburg--Correspondence, 1923-1928 (Box 93)
      - Lynchburg--Correspondence, 1929-1934 (Box 93)
      - Norfolk--Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 94)
      - Norfolk--Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 94)
      - Norfolk--Correspondence, 1926-1928 (Box 94)
      - Norfolk--Correspondence, 1929-1933 (Box 94)
      - Petersburg--Correspondence, 1920-1923 (Box 94)
      - Portsmouth--Correspondence, 1923-1933 (Box 94)
      - Radford, [East Radford] 1921-1924 (Box 94)
      - Roanoke--Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 94)
      - Roanoke--Correspondence, 1922 (Box 94)
      - Roanoke--Correspondence, 1923-1932 (Box 94)
      - Shawsville, 1922-1927 (Box 94)
      - Williamsburg, 1920-1924 (Box 94)
      - Winchester, 1920-1923 (Box 94)
    - City/County Leagues (Box 95)
      - Charlottesville/Albemarle--Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 95)
      - Charlottesville/Albemarle--Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 95)
      - Charlottesville/Albemarle--Correspondence, 1925-1932 (Box 95)
      - Chatham/Pittsylvania Co., 1921-1923 (Box 95)
      - Cherrydale/Arlington Co., 1922-1931 (Box 95)
      - Danville/Pittsylvania Co., 1920-1924 (Box 95)
      - Gretna/Pittsylvania Co., 1920-1924 (Box 95)
      - Newport News/Warwick, 1922 (Box 95)
      - Norfolk/Princess Anne Co.--Correspondence, 1920-1933 (Box 95)
      - Roanoke/Salem Co.--Correspondence, 1921-1924 (Box 95)
      - Staunton/August Co., 1920-1923 (Box 95)
      - Suffolk/Nanesmond Co., 1922-1924 (Box 95)
    - County Leagues (Box 95)
      - Accomack, 1920-1924 (Box 95)
      - Alleghany [Clifton Forge League], 1921-1924 (Box 95)
      - Amherst, 1922 (Box 95)
      - Appomattox, 1921-1924 (Box 95)
      - Augusta, 1921-1923 (Box 95)
      - Bath, 1922 (Box 95)
      - Bedford--Correspondence, report, 1921-1925 (Box 95)
      - Brunswick, 1921-1924 (Box 95)
      - Buchanan, 1921 (Box 95)
      - Buckingham, 1921-1924 (Box 95)
      - Campbell, 1921-1922 (Box 95)
      - Charlotte, 1920-1922 (Box 95)
      - Charles City, 1921, 1926 (Box 95)
      - Chesterfield [Chester], 1921-1933 (Box 95)
      - Clarke, 1923 (Box 95)
      - Elizabeth City [Hampton], 1921-1922 (Box 96)
      - Essex, 1921-1923 (Box 96)
      - Fairfax [Providence League], 1920-1927 (Box 96)
      - Fauquier [Marshall and Scott Branch], 1921-1925 (Box 96)
      - Floyd, 1921 (Box 96)
      - Gloucester, 1921-1922 (Box 96)
      - Greensville, 1921, 1924 (Box 96)
      - Goochland, 1921 (Box 96)
      - Hanover [Ashland Civic League, Cold Harbor, Patrick Henry], 1921-1933 (Box 96)
      - Henrico [Rio Vista, Tuckahoe, Varina Leagues], 1921-1924 (Box 96)
      - Henry, 1920-1922 (Box 96)
      - James City, 1921 (Box 96)
      - King William, 1923 (Box 96)
      - Lancaster, 1921-1922 (Box 96)
      - Loudoun, 1920-1924 (Box 96)
      - Louisa, 1921-1923 (Box 96)
      - Madison, 1920, 1926 (Box 96)
      - Matthews, 1921-1922 (Box 96)
      - Mecklenburg, 1920-1922 (Box 96)
      - Montgomery, 1921-1923 (Box 96)
      - Nelson [Faber League?]--Correspondence, 1924 (Box 96)
      - Northampton, 1920-1924 (Box 96)
      - Orange, 1923 (Box 96)
      - Pittsylvania [Chatham, Greenfield], 1920-1924 (Box 96)
      - Prince George, 1921 (Box 96)
      - Prince William, 1921-1922 (Box 96)
      - Pulaski, 1920 (Box 96)
      - Rockbridge, 1922 (Box 96)
      - Russell, 1921 (Box 96)
      - Smyth, 1920-1921 (Box 96)
      - Southampton, 1925 (Box 96)
      - Surrey [Claremont League], 1921-1925 (Box 96)
      - Tazewell, 1921-1924 (Box 96)
      - Warren, 1921-1923 (Box 96)
      - Washington, 1922 (Box 96)
      - Wise, 1921-1927 (Box 96)
  - Subseries G: University of Virginia File--University Extension Division, undated, 1920-1938
    - Institute of Citizenship and Government (Box 97)
      - Bulletins, Correspondence, Memoranda, Programs, Miscellaneous, 1923 (Box 97)
    - Institute of Public Affairs (Box 97)
      - Addresses, 1931 (Box 97)
      - Circulars, undated (Box 97)
      - Conferences "Adult Education," 1933 (Box 97)
      - Conferences "Studying Public Affairs the Year Around," 1932 (Box 97)
      - Correspondence--Adèle Clark, 1927-1938 (Box 97)
      - Director Correspondence, 1932 (Box 97)
      - Draft Correspondence and Notes--Adèle Clark, undated (Box 97)
      - Invitations, Membership Lists, Newspaper Clippings, Publications, undated (Box 97)
      - Lesson Outlines, undated (Box 97)
      - Proceedings and Roundtables, undated (Box 97)
    - Office of the Instructor (Box 97)
      - Correspondence, 1920-1924, 1925-1933 (Box 97)
    - Proceedings of the School of Citizenship, 1920, 1923 (Box 97)
    - Program--"Know Your League," undated (Box 97)
    - Publications, 1923-1932 (Box 98)
    - "Ten Practical Lessons for Virginia Citizens," undated (Box 98)
  - Subseries H: Other Organizations, undated, 1915-1956
    - Agriculture, Department of--Bureau of Home Economics, undated, 1929 (Box 98)
    - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1922-1925 (Box 98)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, undated (Box 98)
    - American Foundation, undated, 1927-1928 (Box 98)
    - American Game Protection Association, 1922 (Box 98)
    - Better Government League, 1926-1927 (Box 98)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace "International Conciliation," 1915-1929 (Box 98)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co., 1922 (Box 98)
    - Citizens Clearinghouse on Public Education, undated (Box 98)
    - Citizenship Conference, 1923 (Box 98)
    - Clearing Committee for Organizations Supporting Reciprocal Trade, 1947 (Box 98)
    - Commerce, Department of, 1932 (Box 98)
    - Co-Operative Education Association of Virginia--Annual Reports, Bulletins, Memoranda, Minutes, Publications, 1923-1932 (Box 98)
    - Crittenton [Florence] Mission--Annual Report, Biennial Report, 1927, 1922-1924 (Box 99)
    - Democratic State Central Committee correspondence--[Mary E. Pidgeon 1921], 1921-1925 (Box 99)
    - Federal Board for Vocational Education [Division of Civilian Vocational Rehabilitation], 1924 (Box 99)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America "Information Service" Bulletins (Box 99)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 99)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America Publications, undated, 1923-1925 (Box 99)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 99)
      - Bulletins, Memoranda, Newspaper Clippings (Box 99)
      - Information Service Bulletins, Reports, 1925-1935 (Box 99)
      - News Bulletins, 1923-1934 (Box 99)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 99)
      - Publications, 1923-1931 (Box 99)
    - General Defense Committee, 1922 (Box 100)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1924-1933 (Box 100)
    - Interior, Department of--Bureau of Education--Bulletins, 1929-1930 (Box 100)
    - International Woman Suffrage Alliance, 1921-1926 (Box 100)
    - Inter-Racial Cooperation, Commission on, 1920, 1924-1925 (Box 100)
    - Labor, Department of (Box 100)
      - Women's/Children's Bureau (Box 100)
        - Bulletins, Charts, Circulars, undated, 1920-1932 (Box 100)
        - Publications [Children's], undated, 1919-1931 (Box 100)
        - Publications [Women's] (1 of 2), undated, 1920-1921 (Box 100)
        - Publications [Women's] (2 of 2), undated, 1940-1942 (Box 100)
    - Labor, Department of (Box 101)
      - Southern Regional Conferences on Labor Standards, 1935-1936 (Box 101)
    - League of Nations Association (Box 101)
      - Commission Reports, 1923-1925 (Box 101)
      - Memoranda, Miscellaneous (Box 101)
      - News Bulletins, 1923-1933 (Box 101)
      - Pamphlets, Publications (1 of 3), undated, 1924-1932 (Box 101)
      - Pamphlets, Publications (2 of 3), undated, 1923-1924 (Box 101)
      - Pamphlets, Publications (3 of 3), undated, 1933 (Box 101)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities (Box 101)
    - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, Inc., 1926 (Box 101)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1926 (Box 101)
    - National Association of Manufactures, 1926 (Box 101)
    - National Association of Postal Supervisors--Richmond Branch, 1936 (Box 101)
    - National Child Labor Committee, undated, 1924-1930 (Box 101)
    - National Child Labor Committee--Publications, 1924-1927 (Box 101)
    - National Civil Service Reform League, undated, 1922-1924 (Box 102)
    - National Committee on Federal Legislation for Birth Control, 1933 (Box 102)
    - National Committee on the Causes and Cures of War (Box 102)
      - Bulletins, memorandum, Reading Course Lists, Miscellaneous, 1926-1935 (Box 102)
      - Conference Pamphlets and Programs undated, 1925-1931 (Box 102)
      - Conference Reports, 1925, 1926, 1928 (Box 102)
    - National Consumers' League, undated, 1923 (Box 102)
    - National Council for the Prevention of War [Reduction of Armaments] (Box 103)
      - Handbills, Memoranda, Pamphlets, undated, 1921-1931 (Box 103)
      - Publications, Bulletin, News Bulletin, 1922-1930 (Box 103)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, 1924 (Box 103)
    - National Economic League, undated, 1925, 1932 (Box 103)
    - National Education Association, 1923 (Box 103)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Inc., 1930-1931 (Box 103)
    - National Interracial Conference, 1928-1929 (Box 103)
    - National Kindergarten Association, undated, 1922 (Box 103)
    - National Municipal League, 1922-1923 (Box 103)
    - National Popular Government League, 1927-1932 (Box 103)
    - National Recovery Administration, 1933 (Box 103)
    - National Tax Association, undated, 1919 (Box 103)
    - National Woman's Party, 1921-1931 (Box 103)
    - National Woman's Party-- Equal Rights, 1927 (Box 103)
    - National Women's Trade Union League (Box 104)
      - Bulletins, Newsletters, Miscellaneous, undated, 1922-1934 (Box 104)
      - Life and Labor Bulletins, 1923-1929, 1930-1932, 1933-1944 (Box 104)
      - Pamphlets, Proceedings, undated, 1922, 1924 (Box 104)
    - Norfolk Women's Registration Committee, undated (Box 104)
    - Order of Railway Conductors, 1930 (Box 104)
    - Organizations Associated for Ratification of the Child Labor Amendment [Women's Committee for the Children's Amendment, 1924], 1925-1926 (Box 104)
    - Proportional Representation League, 1924 (Box 104)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1932 (Box 105)